export const generalQuestions = [
    {
        question: " What is meant by the Instagram algorithm and how does it work?",
        answer:
            "  Instagram algorithm refers to the criteria by which Instagram assesses the engagement" +
            " on each account. If Instagram discovers that you have a high engagement " +
            "and that you meet its criteria, it will send the posts to other users' feeds," +
            " encouraging them to view, like, and comment.",
        index: 0,
    },
    {
        question:
            "What are hashtags and what do they do?",
        answer: <div>
            <p>Instagram hashtags are words or phrases that are trending on the platform. Using them on your posts can
                make it easy for Instagram to find your page. As a result, people can give your posts likes and views.
                They can become your followers, talk about your account, and enhance engagement.</p>
            <p>Buy Instagram auto likes and watch the likes on your account grow as well as the number of posts you like
                as.</p>
        </div>,
        index: 1,
    },
    {
        question:
            "What does engagement in Instagram mean? ",
        answer: <div>
            <p>In Instagram, engagement refers to the number of likes, views, and comments on your post. Very low
                engagement can make it hard for you to gain social media popularity.</p>
            <p>If you aspire to become an influencer, you must aim for more engagements in your account. This is why it
                is important to buy automatic Instagram likes. It helps increase engagement without you exerting much
                effort.</p>
            <p>Once you have paid for auto likes, we help you make likes views and relevant comments to content relevant
                to yours. You can expect the recipients of your likes to do the same, increasing the likes, views, and
                comments on your Instagram posts.</p>
            <p>You can get high engagement if you get comments that are t least 10 percent of the likes. If you garnered
                200 likes, getting 20 relevant comments could be described as high engagement.</p>
        </div>,
        index: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "Can be buying Instagram likes, views, and followers benefit me even if my account is private? ",
        answer:
            "Both private and public Instagram accounts will benefit from a boost from us." +
            " Yet, private accounts will have limited exposure while public ones can be seen" +
            " by everyone using the platform. Apparently, creating a public IG" +
            " account will help you succeed in your online business endeavors. ",
        index: 3,
    },
    {
        question:
            "I have made an order for Instagram likes, views, and followers. When can I see the result?",
        answer:
            "We work on boosting the online attention on your Instagram the moment we get" +
            " your order. We aim for likes and other IG engagement from real consumers." +
            " Your posts must encourage your followers to comment or react to them." +
            " When your active followers increases through the exposure we make, " +
            "you can see positive results after a few days and track the improvement.",
        index: 4,
    },
    {
        question:
            "What is the perfect time to post my Instagram story?",
        answer: <div>
            <p>You should know that the right time to post is when many Instagram users are online. Even if you bought
                your Instagram views, knowing the best time to show the world your amazing content can make you an
                internet celebrity.</p>
            <p>Some Instagram users prefer to be online in the morning, mostly between 8 to 9, or in the evening, at the
                same time. You can plan ahead of the posting of your content so that it can be done even if you are at
                work.</p>
        </div>,

        index: 5,
    },
    {
        question: "Can I see who watched my Instagram story?",
        answer:
            "The people who viewed your story will be visible to you for up to 48 hours. You need to open your story and swipe the screen. The username of those who watched your video and their number will appear. Just open your story and swipe the screen.",
        index: 6,
    },
    /* {
         question:
             "What is the Best Way to Collaborate with Celebrities and Influencers?",
         answer:
             "The first step for a successful collaboration with celebrities and influencers on Instagram is that you need to find the ones that express your values and personality. If you do that, an influencer will provide you with much-needed social proof, which is the best way to promote your product or service. However, if you fail in collaborating with an influencer that is close to your brand image, their audience will just dismiss your product or service.\n" +
             "In case you are an influencer, you should also think similarly. There is no pressure for you to partner with brands that don’t represent your values. Your audience follows you because you are authentic and you stand for the things you promote. If you are disingenuous, then your image will suffer and you will lose a significant number of followers.",
         index: 7,
     },
     {
         question: "How to Establish an Unforgettable Brand?",
         answer:
             "Establishing an unforgettable brand is a sure way to get Instagram followers. When users find a brand they like, they will return for more. Below, you will find tips to build your brand, gain more followers, and increase your ROI. \n" +
             "•\tPost Frequently and Be Consistent \n" +
             "When you are building an Instagram account, you should always keep a schedule and be consistent. Don’t overthink what you are going to post. Make sure that you regularly publish new content and that you keep your posts consistent.\n" +
             "•\tBoost your Posts with Hashtags" +
             "Hashtags begin with the # symbol and they are used to find similar posts on Instagram and other social media. With these tools, you can help other users find and follow your account. With the right use of a hashtag, you can also become a part of your niche’s community and create one of your own.\n" +
             "•\tHost Giveaways" +
             "There is no denying that users love to enter giveaways. For this reason, social media are full of brands that host contests for various products. The only thing that you need to do is to ask your users to like, share, and follow the post of your giveaway. This simple strategy will dramatically increase the number of your followers with the minimum cost.\n",
         index: 8,
     },
     {
         question: "Is There a Way to Make my Posts Go Viral?",
         answer:
             "Social media platforms have millions of users and so, every successful post has the chance to go viral. However, you can’t know beforehand which post is going to get shared. Users are unpredictable and sometimes your quick posts become more successful than the ones you took the extra effort to create. Even though we can’t be sure of what makes a post go viral, there are certain trends that consistently bring a lot of shares.\n" +
             "Some posts that get always shared on social media are the following:" +
             "•\tMotivational and funny quotes" +
             "•\tMemes" +
             "•\tTutorials and DIY projects" +
             "•\tUnique and original photos" +
             "•\tFunny videos and fail compilations" +
             "•\tBehind the scenes footage" +
             "•\tUser-generated content" +
             "•\tSocial Media Challenges" +
             "One thing that you need to do no matter your posts is to always brand your images. This way, even if your post gets shared, all users will know that it’s your creation.\n" +
             <b/> +
             "Growing the Number of your Followers\n" +
             "Nevertheless, there is one thing that will definitely make your brand strong on Instagram and that is a huge number of followers. Nowadays, you can do that in multiple ways, by getting followers organically, by buying Instagram followers or buying Instagram likes. Buying your following should be the first thing on your list when establishing your brand. If you take extra care to create content that your audience is going to like and appreciate, then the number of your followers will constantly increase.\n",
         index: 9,
     },
     {
         question: "Will Working with An Agency Bring Me Better Results?",
         answer:
             "   Instagram doesn’t have any limits as to who can post on the platform. This means that everyone has the potential of becoming an influencer if he finds a way to attract users’ attention. For example, a teenager can gain a lot of attention by posting consistent content that users like, while a big company struggles to gain any traffic.\n" +
             "For this reason, companies that want to build a presence on Instagram, usually work with an agency that will help them grow their account. The agency has professionals that know how to make any account stand out from the competition and start gaining the audience’s attention.\n" +
             "•\tCan I buy Instagram followers as a Company?" +
             "As a company on Instagram, you face a lot of competition. In your case, an agency will give you the right solutions for your industry. The agency will create a plan for the development of and organic content that will boost your account. This way, you will learn how to gain followers and how to create content that gets likes. In addition to this, you can buy real followers and Instagram likes from tagiamtop.com, the best agency that provides you with followers and likes. By doing this, you enhance your brand and create opportunities for more future sales. \n" +
             "•\tCan I get Even more Followers as an Influencer?" +
             "If you are an aspiring influencer, then you are probably thinking of new ways to get more Instagram followers. In this case, working with an agency is the best idea. They will guide you to buy real Instagram followers that will boost your account and your brand’s reputation.  More followers mean a greater engagement rate, and this also means an increase in your prices.\n",
         index: 10,
     },
     {
         question: "What is the Reason Why I Am Losing Followers?",
         answer:
             "The Instagram algorithm periodically goes through the accounts of its users. They examine the accounts that other users marked as spam and sweep them. If some of your followers are accounts like this, you might notice a sudden drop in followers.  If you notice that this thing happened within 30 days after you have purchased our services, we will make sure to replenish your followers.",
         index: 11,
     },
     {
         question:
             "Is There a Way to Cancel the Followers That I Purchased from TagIamTop",
         answer:
             "All of the followers we provide you are real Instagram users. This means that we can’t transfer or remove them. If there are some individual accounts you wish to remove from your follower list, you can block them one by one.",
         index: 12,
     },
     {
         question: "What Can I Do if I Don’t Want Follower Replenishment?",
         answer:
             "If you wish to stop follower replenishment, you should let us know by sending an email at support@tagiamtop.com.",
         index: 13,
     },
     {
         question: "How Often Do You Conduct Follower Replenishment?",
         answer:
             "We make sure to conduct follower replenishment every 24 hours. Once we detect a follower drop, our system begins the process.",
         index: 14,
     },
     {
         question: "Is there a Limit to the Followers I can Buy?",
         answer:
             "There is no limit as to how many times you can purchase our services. However, the cumulative number of followers should not surpass 100,000 followers within 30 days.",
         index: 15,
     },
     {
         question:
             "Do I Need to Provide Your with Passwords And Credentials To Purchase Your Services?",
         answer:
             "The only thing that we require of your is your account’s username. You don’t have to provide us with your passwords or your other credentials.",
         index: 16,
     },
     {
         question: "How Can You Provide Real Likes from Real Accounts?",
         answer:
             "We have worked hard to build a large network to provide you with superior services. Our numerous contacts among Instagram users allows us to get you all the real likes and followers you need.",
         index: 17,
     },
     {
         question: "What Are the Payment Methods you are Accepting?",
         answer:
             "At the moment, you can settle your bills with Cryptocurrencies,  and all cards. Nevertheless, we are planning on introducing more payment methods in the future to add more convenience to you.",
         index: 18,
     },*/
];

export const billingQuestions = [
    {
        question: "What Are the Payment Methods you are Accepting?",
        answer:
            "At the moment, you can settle your bills with Cryptocurrencies,  and all cards. Nevertheless, we are planning on introducing more payment methods in the future to add more convenience to you.",
        index: 0,
    },
];

export const frequentQuestions = [
    {
        question: "How important is my being high visibility online?",
        answer:
            "Almost everything happens online. Let internet users find you or your IG business account by gaining lots of new subscribers, followers and activity with your profile. Instagram has billions of users worldwide. If lots of people to use posts and videos on your profile, you will find your business highly searchable three days after you have bought followers, viewers, and likes. These IG accounts are real and active. As the result, it will do good things to your online presence. ",
        index: 0,
    },
    {
        question: "How can I purchase likes, followers, and views from Instagram?",
        isOpen: false,
        answer:
            "Building an Instagram profile and growing it can take time. It might take months for you to get noticed online. You can post a lot of photos, stories, video and other creatives but but not getting organic traffic reach. It's really hard to get level to be seen on Instagram. We offer various packages of likes, auto-likes, comments, views, and followers that can enhance your engagement, get people interested in following you or seeing your ads. How? The only thing you should do is to select relevant hashtags that can catch the attention and interest of all target Instagram subscriber. We do the rest. We make sure that there will develop your profile and encourage others to interact with your posts.",
        index: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "Can you help me with some issues with my Instagram account? ",
        answer:
            "As we put into use the likes, comments, and followers we provided you, you might get swamped with numerous activities on your account. You will be inundated with notifications every time you get a view or like. We are always here to help you to get a lot of likes or followers. Rest assured that our expert support team will work with you to accomplish your goals. Our platform is making things convenient and fruitful for you. Together, let us watch your online presence grow.",
        index: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "What is your reason for selling Instagram likes or followers?",
        isOpen: false,
        answer: <div>
            <p>We have several reasons for selling Instagram activity. People like you need them to</p>
            <ul>
                <li>Grow their online presence.</li>
                <li>Build their customer base if they are running a business</li>
                <li>Show their popularity on social media and become an influencer.</li>
            </ul>
            <p> As soon as users have started to view your photos and to put likes their friends can notice it and pay
                attention to your profile. The same is true with influencers. People will buy whatever you endorse. We
                enhance your online visibility by making sure that a big number of IG users will draw attention to you
                on the World Wide Web.
            </p>
        </div>


        ,
        index: 3,
    },
    {
        question: "Can be buying Instagram likes, views, and followers benefit me even if my account is private? ",
        isOpen: false,
        answer:
            "Both private and public Instagram accounts will benefit from a boost from us. Yet, private accounts will have limited exposure while public ones can be seen by everyone using the platform. " +
            "Apparently, creating a public IG account will help you succeed in your online business endeavors. ",
        index: 4,
    },
    {
        question: "I have made an order for Instagram likes, views, and followers. When can I see the result? ",
        isOpen: false,
        answer:
            "We work on boosting the online attention on your Instagram the moment we get your order. We aim for likes and other IG engagement from real consumers. Your posts must encourage your followers to comment or react to them. When your active followers increases through the exposure we make, you can see positive results after a few days and track the improvement.",
        index: 5,
    },
];
